const qandA = [
{
    question: "which of these fruits are rich in vitamin-C?",
    option: ["mango", "apple", "Orange", "pineapple"],
    answer: "Orange",
 },
 {
   question: "We need ____ glasses of water everyday?",
   option: ["12", "8", "6", "10"],
   answer: "8",
 },
 {
   question: "Which has less sugar?",
   option: ["Apple juice" ,"Orange juice", "pineapple juice", "They are about the same"],
   answer: "Orange juice",
 },
 {
    question: "What are calories really?",
    option: ["Energy", "Fat", "Sugar"],
    answer: "Fat",
 },
 {
    question: "Bananas are rich in?",
    option: ["Protein", "Carbohydrates", "fats"],
    answer: "Carbohydrates",
 },
 {
    question: "Green leafy vegetables are rich in _____?",
    option: ["Protein", "Iron", "Fat", "None of the above"],
    answer: "Iron",
 },
 {
    question: "Which is the most important meal of the day?",
    option: ["Dinner", "Lunch", "Breakfast"],
    answer: "Breakfast",
 },
 {
    question: "which has fewer calories?",
    option: ["Baked potatoe", "Brown rice", "They are about the same"],
    answer: "Brown rice",
 },
 {
    question: "What does your body need more?",
    option: ["Fruits", "Vegetables", "Water"],
    answer: "Water",
 },
 {
    question: "which has less sugar?",
    option: ["Vanilla ice cream", "Vanilla frozen yogurt", "They are about the same"],
    answer: "They are about the same",
 },
 {
    question: "Which of these diets is the worst for your long term weight loss?",
    option: ["Atkins", "South Beach", "Slimfast"],
    answer: "Slimfast",
 },
 {
    question: "The nutrient that is stored in the body for future use is?",
    option: ["protein", "Fats", "Carbohydrate", "None of the above"],
    answer: "Fats",
 },
]